Smokebox
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The smokebox is difficult to explain, but simply put, it is the room that pulls away combustion gases from the [:煙管]boiler tubes[:] to be exhausted to the chimney. I think that's as simple as it can be."

【双鉄】
"By exhausting it from the chimney, the [:火室]firebox[:] will get fresh air into it then?"

【ハチロク】
"Correct. That is why cleaning the smokebox for good ventilation is also crucial in order to efficiently run a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]. You can also the [:ブロワー]blower[:] header for more details."
