Coasting
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When steam is pushed into the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] to spin them, causing the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] to run, it is called powering."

【れいな】
"Diesel [:気動車]railcars[:] and electric trains are the same in that when the engine or motor drive the driving wheel, it is called powering. So when the driving wheels aren't powered and you are running only with inertia, it's called coasting, or inertial driving."

【ポーレット】
"The friction between the tracks and driving wheel is very small, so there's not that much need to continue powering. A lot of railcars use coasting very often."
