Axle Box
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The round stick that connects the [:動輪]drive wheels[:] on both sides is the axle. The axle box, simply put, is a device that holds that axle."

【双鉄】
"In the case of [:8620]8620[:], the foundation of the train that is the [:台枠]frame[:] has the wheel set on both sides, sandwiched by the corresponding axle box that supports it."

【ポーレット】
"In short, the axle box connects the driving wheels together and it holds it down so it doesn't accidentally slip off."
