Turn Table
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Railcars like the [:8620]8620[:] that only has the [:運転台]driver stand[:] on one side, in other words, a train that has a clear front and rear, must use some method to turn around in another direction."

【ポーレット】
"The turn table is a device that can efficiently turn it around. Simply place the railcar over the turn table and turn it 180 degrees. The turn table name is commonly used."
