Engineer Assistant
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The engineer assistant shovels in coal for the locomotive, checks the boiler water level, and also manages the steam pressure and ventilation. To make sure the combustion and steam is constant is the greatest responsibility of the engineer assistant."

【双鉄】
"Assistant. As the word states, a good [:機関士]engineer[:] assistant smooths out the work of the [:機関士]engineer[:]. The [:機関士]engineer[:] assistant no ordinary helper. They stand alongside the [:機関士]engineer[:] and support the operation."
