Post-work Examination
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"In the past, Ohitoyo Railway only had [:キハ07]Kiha 07[:]-s, so we were unable to do alternating examinations. Now that we can reinforce the system to do inspections, we do the examination after the operation for the day ends."

【れいな】
"And that's the post-work examination. But the actual work is no different from the maintenance inspections."

【ハチロク】
"Yes. Taking time to double-check things can raise the accuracy even with a smaller staff. I think it's a wonderful thing."
