Mas-con
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"The term 'mas-con' is the short form of master controller. It helps controls the railcar semi-automatically. The name literally is its function."

【れいな】
"[:キハ07]Kiha 07[:] or [:8620]8620[:] use gears changes, fuel injection management, and [:ブレーキ]braking[:], but with a single lever of the mas-con you can do all that."

【ポーレット】
"For more details, you can look at the entry for the [:ダイコン]di-con[:]."
