Power Car
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"A power car has the driving force that powers the driving wheel to run on its own. This applies to locomotives, diesel cars, and electric trains alike. In other words, all cars that draw passenger and freight cars are all power cars. Furthermore, a power car with operative controls are usually referred to as a 'driving car'."
