Bypass Valve
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When in [:絶気運転]inertial driving[:], no steam will be going into the cylinder. But even in [:絶気運転]inertial driving[:], [:粘着力]adhesion[:] will be maintained so the rotating of the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] connected to the [:クロスヘッド]crosshead[:] will move the piston."

【双鉄】
"Being in inertial movement means the cylinder is closed. In that state, if the piston moves, the enclosed air inside the piston will be pressurized. If the reverse side continues to become a vacuum, that may damage the cylinder."

【ハチロク】
"To prevent that, the air in the front and back must have a valve that can bypass the air in the front and back so that the piston can move freely.　The bypass valve cock is what controls this bypass valve."
