Draft
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"In a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:], maintain ventilation is needed to burn coal. There is the [:ブロワー]blower[:] device that is used by exhausting the steam inside the boiler out the chimney. That action itself is called a draft."

【双鉄】
"The [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]'s puffing sound is caused by this draft. It is usually referred to as the draft sound. The other hissing sound, which is the [:ブラスト]blast[:] sound can be seen more in detail in that entry."
