First Class Shipping
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"First class shipping is one method of transporting railcars. The towing train and the towed train stay on the tracks. Because it tows to transport it, train photo enthusiasts really love that."

【ハチロク】
"Second class shipping involves a special [:貨車]freight car[:] that carries the railcar. Third class shipping doesn't use the railways and transports the railcar by automobile or boat."
