Blockade
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"In order to secure the safety of the trains, the most basic thing is a blockade."

【ポーレット】
"For example, you cut off a section between two stations and when a [:列車]train[:] enters that section, no other [:列車]train[:] will be allowed inside that blockaded section. That is the blockade rule."

【ハチロク】
"Meaning the blockaded section is completely exclusive to the [:列車]train[:] in that section. Being such an exclusive method, this allows the prevention of the danger of a collision."
