Flange
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When the centrifugal force pushes on the train, it can shake the body and cause a derailment. In order to prevent the wheels from being derailed, the inside of the wheels have parts that jut out to catch onto the tracks. That is called the flange."

【ポーレット】
"For example, when turning right, the body and [:列車]train[:] itself will have forces pushing it to the left and off the tracks. When that happens, the left wheel's flange on the inner side will hit the inner side of the left rails to prevent derailment."

【ハチロク】
"Because of its function, it's one the places that wear down the quickest. That's why locomotives that run extended distances have tempered flanges for higher hardness and is also maintained regularly."
