Overlapping Position
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The [:ブレーキ]brakes[:] for a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] is an air [:ブレーキ]brake[:]. Pressurized air inside the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] valves are what applies the stopping power inside the mechanism."

【双鉄】
"When the air pressure goes down in the brake tube, the brake power increases. To loosen the brakes, you increase air pressure in the brake tubes. With this mechanism, even if the brake tubes are damaged, in an [:非常]emergency[:], the train will stop automatically."

【ハチロク】
"The overlapping position is where the pressurized air is neither increased nor decreased. By quickly moving the [:常用]service brake[:] position quickly, you can maintain the [:ブレーキ]braking[:] power that way."
