Loop Line
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Railcars do not travel well on steep slopes. In order to avoid those slopes, the tracks are laid out in a roundabout way so that the incline or decline is much more gradual. This method is commonly used."

【ポーレット】
"Consecutive gradual slopes going in a loop are what we call a loop line. In order to clear steep slopes, loop lines or switchbacks are two of the most common methods."
