Engine Shed/Engine Depot
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"To be exact, the engine shed is the base where the locomotive is stored at. But in fact, it is also the section in which the passenger or [:貨車]freight[:] train is responsible for and its placement of its equipment and personnel. The entire package is called the 'engine shed'."

【れいな】
"For Ohitoyo Railway's [:キハ07]Kiha 07[:]-s, it's actually considered to belong to the Ohitoyo diesel [:気動車]railcar[:] shed. But when asked what it is, Reina says 'Ohitoyo Engine Shed' since that's more common."
