9600
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Model 9600 is the first domestic freight [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] and are also known as the sister units of Model [:8620]8620[:]. They are my hardworking sisters."

【ポーレット】
"Being forced out of use by D51, they have been pushed into the branch lines all over Japan. But that is also why they were the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotives[:] in use until the very end of the [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:]."

【ハチロク】
"Correct. Domestic [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotives[:] can all be considered my little sisters, but out of them, I have the most affinity for and am most proud of Model 9600."
