Maintenance Body
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"We [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] change to this body for railcar maintenance, helping with [:機関士]engineer[:], driver, [:車掌]conductor[:], and station duties. The maintenance body, as it is called, is the size close to a human."

【れいな】
"Compared to the operation body, the sensors aren't as good, but in exchange the fingertips are much more deft."

【ハチロク】
"The right body for the right job. Just like how humans change tools depending on the job, we change bodies."
