Fly Ash
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Fly ash is the ash from burned coal from inside the boiler of a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]."

【双鉄】
"Depending on the shoveling or draft, the temperature changes and vibrations from running, and the quality of the coal itself sometimes yields clumps like pumice instead of the sandy ash."

【ハチロク】
"During the [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:], some railway fans actually wanted the fly ash. Oh, I mean. I'm sure that even for Ohitoyo Railway, some people would like to receive it to commemorate riding the train."
