Blower
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The blower is a device that secures a draft so that coal can consistently combust in the [:火室]firebox[:]. The blower is powered by the exhaust from the cylinder while running. When the train is stopped, the steam from the boiler will be exhausted from the chimney."

【双鉄】
"And the [:煙管]boiler tubes[:] connected to the [:火室]firebox[:] in the space called the [:煙室]smokebox[:] will be close to a vacuum. A powerful intake will then occur to add fresh air into the [:火室]firebox[:]. That's how it works."

【ハチロク】
"The blower is the name of the device that was just explained. To use blower at will, you turn what is called the blower valve."
