Switchback
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"Railcars typically are not good with climbing steep slopes. But when it must be done, there is a track-side mechanism that makes it easier. And that is the switchback."

【ハチロク】
"Specifically, it lays the tracks in a zigzag way so that it goes back and forth over the rails to allow the [:列車]train[:] to climb to a higher position easier."
