Main Building
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"The main building refers to the main structure of the railway station. The ticketing gate, waiting room, ticket sales area, and the stationmaster office are part of this building. At Ohitoyo-onsen Station, the Rail Shop is a part of the station's main building."

【ハチロク】
"During my time at the Imperial Railway, we called it the principal building. Terms and their usages appear to change depending on the era and location."
