Formation
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The formation refers to how the [:列車]train[:] cars are set up. If the [:列車]train[:] is composed of six connected cars, it is a six car formation. A [:列車]train[:] with only one railcar is called a one-car formation."

【ポーレット】
"By the way, [:列車]trains[:] refer to railcars that follow a specific diagram schedule. Railcars that are connected but do not run are not [:列車]trains[:]. But even if it is a single railcar that follows the schedule, it is called a [:列車]train[:]."

【ハチロク】
"For more details, see the entry for [:列車]trains[:]."
