Engineer
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The engineer is the one in charge of the operation and controls of the locomotive. They are the humans who operate all things locomotive."

【双鉄】
"With regards to the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:], driving and controlling the [:蒸気機関車]steam engine[:] are directly related. Increasing the output of the [:蒸気機関車]steam engine[:] will make the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] run. To stop, you reduce the output and control the [:ブレーキ]brake[:]. That's the general gist of it."

【ハチロク】
"In emergencies, the [:機関助士]engineer assistant[:] also take over the job of the engineer. [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] stick to being helper for the engineer. The brain of the locomotive must still be the engineer."
