Cylinder Cock
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"In a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:], the pistons propelled by steam move back and forth to move the [:動輪]driving wheel[:]. In order to not let steam escape, the piston moves inside a steel tube called the cylinder."

【双鉄】
"The steam that moves the piston will become water once it cools. And when the cylinder fills with water, it will hit the piston, causing it to break down. That is why the cylinder must be drained."

【ハチロク】
"The valve that opens to drain the cylinder water is called the cylinder cock. To be exact, it's called the cylinder drain valve."
