Shoveling
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Throwing in coal into the [:火室]firebox[:] is called shoveling. This is one of the most basic and ultimate actions needed for the stable operation of the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]."

【日々姫】
"That's why we're trained hard on shoveling itself. Even Ohitoyo Station has its own shoveling practice area where we can train ourselves. That's how important it is."

【双鉄】
"The [:火室]firebox[:] can create a powerful draft, so the trick to shoveling is is to layer it thick to the front, and thinner in the back. Even after shoveling 10 or even 20 tons, Hachiroku would say that you haven't practiced enough."
