Regulator
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"This device adjusts the steam sent into the piston and cylinder to move the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] of a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]. That is the regulator."

【双鉄】
"It's the gas pedal for an automobile. The regulator lever can be pulled to send in steam to increase the acceleration of the locomotive. Push to close it to reduce the steam and to go into [:絶気運転]inertial driving[:]."

【ハチロク】
"Using too much steam will make you go low and accelerating too fast will make stopping harder. Knowing how to use the regulator is one of the most fundamental points of driving a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]."
