Sympathetic Connection
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Sympathetic Connection allows [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] to communicate with each other of their information, senses, and even emotions up to a certain extent."

【れいな】
"The sympathetic connection is convenient, but if the distance is too far, we can't hear each other. And if there's a [:レイルロオド]Raillord[:] that's panicking, we can't receive the connection anymore."

【ハチロク】
"Rumor has it that a safety mechanism activates so that we don't get dragged down with her, but even [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] do not fundamentally understand how this actually works."
