Carriage
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"The carriage is the structure that can be separated from the [:台枠]frame[:] and body. It refers to the suspension portion of a railcar."

【れいな】
"The carriage has the driving wheel, [:ブレーキ]brakes[:], and running devices, which are the devices needed to run. Rather than having the running devices attached to the [:台枠]frame[:], making it a carriage style will allow it to turn easier and have less vibrations."
