Priming
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Priming is a type of boiler accident. When the boiler water is over boiled, the steam mixes with condensation and it exits out of the boiler."

【双鉄】
"Normally, the steam goes to the piston or cylinder section. As a result, it comes out of the chimney as an oily black steam. But this causes the oil to be washed away from the piston and cylinder."

【ハチロク】
"With no oil, the piston and cylinder will burn up. That is why when priming occurs, oil must be injected immediately."
