Slide
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Sliding refers to when the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] is stopped by a braking force and [:粘着力]adhesion[:] is also lost, causing the wheels to slide over the rails."

【ポーレット】
"Once you start sliding, you're helpless until [:粘着力]adhesion[:] returns. And in the meanwhile, the train is completely uncontrollable. It's extremely dangerous because you can do nothing but slide over the rails."

【ハチロク】
"One of the greatest duties of the Raillords is to provide assistance in the prevention of sliding. For more details, please see the entry on [:粘着力]adhesion[:]."
