Smoke Deflector
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Aside from the [:集煙装置]smoke collection device[:], there are many contraptions to prevent smoke from entering the [:運転台]driver stand[:] or [:客車]passenger car[:]. One of those is the smoke deflectors, also known as defs."

【双鉄】
"It is set up in the front of the body to the side of the boiler to surround the chimney. Those two plates of steel are that."

【ハチロク】
"It's quite simple, but extremely effective in practice."
