Air Pump
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"The [:ブレーキ]brake[:] device of a train uses pressurized air. When the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] valve is filled with pressurized air, the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] power will not activate. When pressurized air leaves the, the [:ブレーキ]braking[:] power gets stronger. That is the mechanism."

【れいな】
"The machine that creates the pressurized air is the air pump."

【ハチロク】
"In short, it's a piston pump that is similar to the air pump for bicycles. In the case of the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:], it uses steam to move the piston up and down to pressurize the air in a simply closed system."
