Wheel Tread
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The wheel tread is the part of the railcar's wheels that makes contact with the tracks."

【双鉄】
"The contact surface for the tracks and driving wheels are very small. That is why it is necessary to maintain the condition of the wheel tread for a safe operation of the train."

【ハチロク】
"Supposing that you touch the wheel tread with your oily hands. Even that is enough to affect the [:制動]braking[:] distance by many times. That is how delicate wheel treads are and also crucial."
