Axle Guard
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"While a railcar is in motion, the [:動輪]driving wheels[:] and axles will be subject forces from all directions. To install the [:軸箱]axle box[:], the plate [:台枠]frame[:] must be cut out to make a hole large enough for it."

【双鉄】
"In other words, the [:軸箱]axle box[:] and [:台枠]frame[:] is under an enormous load. In order to prevent damage from that load, a steel part is used to reinforce it. That part, as the name suggests, is the axle guard."

【ハチロク】
"While the axle box is used to reinforce the structure, various springs are used to cushion the impact. And even with all these mechanisms, problems can sometimes occur, showing how much load is placed on these parts."
