Slope Map
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The slope map is also known as the [:縦断面図]longitudinal section map[:]. It is a railway map that shows all the slope changes along the tracks. The changes in slope are all recorded to create this map."

【双鉄】
"Understanding the changes in slope is crucial in controlling the train. That is why an accurate slope map is extremely valuable."
