Frame
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The frame is the hip portion of the railcar. The body is the torso and the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] is the legs. Being the most important foundation, a railcar must have one that is strong and stable."

【ポーレット】
"Railway cars after the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotives[:] have the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] directly attached to the frame, so it has been changed to the [:台車]carriage[:] style. But the importance of the frame still has not changed."

【ハチロク】
"For more details, I suggest you check the entry for [:台車]carriage[:] as well."
