Call-out
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"Call-outs refer to the safety checks and mistake prevention by calling and pointing at the same time. When the signal shows that the train can go, people are familiar with the term, 'all aboard', that is used here."

【ハチロク】
"Speaking of which, when the signal gives a warning to lower the speed to 25 kilometers per hour, the [:機関士]engineer[:] and [:機関士]engineer[:] assistant will both call out 'departure warning'. 'All aboard' is not the only phrase used."
