Adhesion
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Adhesion refers to the friction between the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] and tracks. It's the force that allows the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] to catch onto the tracks. If for whatever reason the adhesion is at zero, the [:動輪]driving wheel[:] will spin, causing a slide over the tracks in a dangerous fashion."

【双鉄】
"The cause of a wheel spin can be if the towed [:貨車]freight car[:] is too heavy, when there is rain, or when some foreign object on the tracks caused the friction to decrease... Is that all?"

【ハチロク】
"Correct. By dealing with each of the causes, maintaining adhesion becomes crucial in operating a locomotive. One of the methods to do so can be seen at the entry for [:砂撒き]sandblasting[:]."
