Driver
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The person who operates [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotives[:] or diesel [:蒸気機関車]locomotives[:] are called [:機関士]engineers[:]. However diesel cars and electric trains which do not have a separate [:運転台]driver stand[:], but rather a driving seat that is in the same structure as the [:客車]passenger car[:]. The people who operate these types of trains are called drivers."

【双鉄】
"As a steam locomotive [:機関士]engineer[:], I get the impression that drivers only need to focus on the driving aspect of the train. Naturally, it is never that simple."

【ハチロク】
"That is correct. An [:機関士]engineer[:] must always directly deal with the locomotive and check its status constantly. There is a reason why these two occupations are given different names."
