Fusible Plug
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] uses the fire and coal, and the combustion gases from fire to boil water and to create steam to run. That is why it is always a risk of abnormal combustion or explosions that is inherent by design."

【双鉄】
"One of the contraptions to prevent that danger is the fusible plug. It is made with cooper or a copper-lead alloy that is easy to melt, and it plugs a hole in the ceiling of the [:火室]firebox[:]."

【ハチロク】
"Normally, the fusible plug is immersed in the boiler water. However, when the water level drops, the fusible plug will be exposed, causing it to melt easily. The [:火室]firebox[:] will then spit steam into the [:運転台]driver stand[:], so the issue will be recognized immediately."
