Shunting Signal
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【れいな】
"When taking out a railcar from the engine shed or to connect a locomotive to a [:貨車]freight car[:] or [:客車]passenger car[:] by moving the locomotive inside the station or engine shed is the action called shunting."

【ハチロク】
"And for that shunting to be done safely, the signals placed on the rails not on the main line, which connects stations to stations, but at the engine shed or within the station are called shunting signals."

【ポーレット】
"While on duty, we can simply call it 'shunting' or switching. If you think of railways when you hear shunting or switching, you're likely a railway fan."
