Single Track
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"Like with the Ohitoyo Railway Yunoi Line, there is only one main line connecting station to station. This is called a single track. If there are two tracks, it's called a double track. If there are 2 pairs of tracks, meaning four parallel tracks, it is called a quadrulpe track. If there are 3 pairs of tracks, it can be called a sextuple track or 3-pair track."

【ハチロク】
"With single tracks, trains on opposite sides would eventually collide at some point. When an express train tries to overtake a regular train, they would also collide. For information on how that is prevented, please see the entry on the [:待避線]sidetrack[:]."
