Ticket Punching
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Ticket punching refers to cutting into the tickets of passengers. It's a railway-related technique that is graceful and easy to see."

【双鉄】
"Graceful? Are you sure about that?"

【ハチロク】
"Well, of course. Prior to the Track Closure Era, the Teiou Station had station workers that could do it in a blink of an eye if they were entrusted with the central ticket gate."
