Limit
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Limits are displayed on signs or signals and the speed limits shown will apply until the next sign."

【れいな】
"If it says Limit 50, then it must be under 50 kilometers per hour. If it says Limit 25, then it must be under 25 kilometers."

【ハチロク】
"If the next sign has a different limit, we will follow the new one. If the speed limit is lifted, we [:喚呼]call out[:] 'limit release' and return to the optimum speed of that railcar."
