Firebox
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The firebox is where coal is shoveled in. In other words, it's the stomach of the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]."

【双鉄】
"The rear part of the [:運転台]driver stand[:] is the mouth of the furnace. You can shovel in coal through there. At the same time, it acts as a vent."

【ハチロク】
"The area around the furnace is covered in water to prevent empty burning. When the furnace is burning dry, the boiler can possibly be destroyed, causing a major accident."
