Reversing Gear
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The reversing gear has the gears forward, neutral, and reverse. At each setting, it changes the amount of steam sent to the cylinder in a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]. [:8620]8620[:] has a screw-type reversing gear where the [:機関士]engineer[:] must spin it around by hand."

【双鉄】
"By adjusting the steam volume with the [:加減弁]regulator[:], the reversing gear manages the intake and exhaust. By matching those two together, it decides the direction and speed of the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:]. Getting a hold of this feeling was extremely difficult."

【ハチロク】
"Many other [:機関士]engineers[:] thought the same. Future locomotives used a lever system with notches to exclude the any sort of control by intuition and became mainstream."
