Brake
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"What we commonly call brakes is air braking or automatic air braking of the object."

【双鉄】
"Inside the brake tube is pressurized air. Try to imagine a structure with the [:制輪子]brake block[:] being lifted up. Using the brakes or if by accident, the pressurized air is removed, the [:制輪子]brake block[:] will make contact with the [:踏面]tracks[:] to apply the breaks."

【ハチロク】
"For more details, take a look at the entries for [:自弁]automatic brake valve[:], [:単弁]independent brake valve[:], [:圧]pressure[:], [:制輪子]brake block[:], and more."
