Line Maintenance
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Line maintenance refers to the important job of maintaining railway tracks, bridges, tunnels, and any other structure from natural disasters and corrosion so that the railways can be operated safely."

【ポーレット】
"The ones who work on the line maintenance are the line maintenance section who operate out of the line maintenance base."

【ハチロク】
"When the line maintenance is not done, it's the same as if the railway company is dead. Repairing the bad parts and constant inspections to prevent issues would be ideal."
