Maintenance Inspection
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【れいな】
"The maintenance inspection is done every day prior to starting operation. The moving parts are checked and corroded parts or used up consumables must be exchanged or replenished."

【ポーレット】
"To be exact, the parts between machines, power transmission device, running device, [:ブレーキ]braking[:] devices, [:連結器]couplers[:], and riggings are inspected without taking them apart."

【ハチロク】
"At the [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:], each locomotive receives the maintenance inspection while passenger and [:貨車]freight cars[:] receive a first-train inspection so that there is no confusion that way."
