Drive Position
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] handle is set on 'drive', it means that the [:ブレーキ]brakes[:] are fully released and air pressure inside the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] valve is full. The state is quite literally the 'drive position'."

【双鉄】
"Pre-departure, during operation, [:絶気運転]inertial driving[:], and right before stopping are times when the [:ブレーキ]brake[:] is set at the drive position."

【ハチロク】
"Stopping with the pressure still full will cause a shock. The stopping while in drive position is done by weight and friction. That is the secret to a passenger-friendly stopping method."
