Di-con
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"A hand throttle that controls the flow of fuel into the engine is called the di-con handle with gears and [:ブレーキ]brakes[:], too. The type of controls that you directly manipulate by hand are all called 'direct controls'."

【れいな】
"Shortened to di-con. [:キハ07]Kiha 07[:] is a di-con style model. But in loose sense of the word, [:8620]8620[:] is also a di-con type."

【ハチロク】
"When most of the driving can be at least partially done by one handle, it was called like the [:マスコン]mas-con[:], or master controller. The di-con came into being to contrast it. During my time, they did not have that sort of name."
