Point
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"Let's say there is a [:待避線]sidetrack[:] away from the main tracks in the line connecting two stations. The junction where the [:列車]train[:] can enter the main line or to go to the [:待避線]sidetrack[:] is called the point."

【ハチロク】
"At the former [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:], we called it the point and crossing. The point and crossing allows the [:列車]train[:] to go into either tracks by switching at will by design."

【れいな】
"The point is dangerous in that there is a danger of derailment. If you pass the point and then back up by mistake, you'd get derailed instantly, did you know?"
