Train Factory
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"A factory that creates railway cars. The former [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:] and large railway companies have their own factories. Of course, each of the train manufacturers have their own."

【ハチロク】
"Regular maintenance and light repair can be done at the engine shed, which is the base of operations. But major service repairs must be done at the factory by sending it back."

【ポーレット】
"But ever since the Track Closure Era, many of the factories went out of business, giving rise to more accidents from a lack of maintenance, further accelerating the Track Closure Era. That negative spiral further shortened the life of the railways. Well, that's what I heard."
