Fire Maintenance
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【双鉄】
"When the fire is extinguished in a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:], it requires a lot of work to reignite it. That is why even if the [:蒸気機関車]locomotive[:] is parked for extended periods of time, the fire is kept burning. This state is called fire maintenance."

【日々姫】
"The one who watches the fire is called the fire watcher. At Ohitoyo Railway, we do this job on rotation, but this is actually tough. Just staring at the fire all night makes you so sleepy."
