Diagram
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Due to the [:共感]sympathetic connection[:] among [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:], whether on a single track or multiple ones, they can adjust accordingly for the most efficient [:列車]train[:] operation."

【れいな】
"But you have to consider the railway company's business and convenience to customers to make it a easy-to-use line. So we have to think of all that to make the diagram that is the railway operation plan."

【ハチロク】
"Under normal circumstances, the [:列車]trains[:] follow the regular diagram schedule. But during seasons with peak tourism or at times of accidents, there will be provisional diagrams applied. For more details, check the entry for [:運転計画]driving plan[:]."
