Storage Helper
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The workers who clean the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] and the engine shed in general are all called Storage Helpers. At the former [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:], in order to become an [:機関士]engineer[:], you go from storage helper, [:機関助士]engineer assistant[:], and then to [:機関士]engineer[:] while taking exams each step of the way."

【双鉄】
"Currently at Ohitoyo Railway, the [:機関士]engineer[:], president, and even the storage helper is the same person. Cleaning a [:蒸気機関車]locomotive[:] is labor-intensive and also dangerous if you're careless."

【ハチロク】
"That is why the unqualified are removed. They must understand the strength and awe of the [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] while they are still a storage helper. Only those who take another step forward can even hope to become an [:機関士]engineer[:]."
