Driving Wheel
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] uses steam from the boiler that is sent to the cylinder. The steam then moves the piston back and forth, which then converts that energy into a rotational movement to the [:クロスヘッド]crosshead[:]. The energy then transfers to the [:主連棒]connecting rod[:] and the driving wheel."

【双鉄】
"And the rotating [:主連棒]connecting rod[:] moves the powered driving wheel, which is called the main driving wheel. From the main driving wheel, the [:連結棒]coupling rod[:] transfers the energy to other driving wheels."

【ハチロク】
"Of course, the main driving wheel is a driving wheel itself. The collection of driving wheels are sometimes called the driving wheel group. For more details, see the entries on the [:主連棒]connecting rod[:], [:シリンダー弁]cylinder[:], [:クロスヘッド]crosshead[:] and more."
