Slope Permillage
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Slopes for railways is not in relation to the ground but with the tracks, parallel to the horizontal surface. The rate of change of the slope by a rate of a thousand is the slope permillage. This is displayed by a change in height after moving one kilometer."

【双鉄】
"So the unit of measurement is per-mil."

【ハチロク】
"Correct. For example, if the change in height is five meters after moving one kilometer, the slop permillage is 'five'. And shown as 'five per-mil'."
