Triangular Junction
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When I was in my prime, railcars only had driving stands or seats on one side. In other words, there is a clear front and back."

【ポーレット】
"For those railcars to change directions, there is a three way triangular junction, also known as the delta line."

【ハチロク】
"Please try to imagine a diagram in how you can switch directions by using the triangle. Here's a hint. Front, reverse, then front again."
