Diesel Railcar
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【れいな】
"Diesel railcars have the driver seat and the [:客車]passenger car[:] together. The internal engine can run on its own."

【ハチロク】
"Depending on the fuel, there can be steam railcars and [:ディーゼル気動車]diesel railcars[:], gasoline railcars, electric railcars. The difference between an electric train and a electric railcar is whether they are powered by electricity from the [:架線]gasen[:] or if it runs using an electric motor with its own generator."

【ポーレット】
"Oh. So an electric train isn't a railcar. Augh... I taught Sotetsu-kun the wrong thing."
