Sidetrack
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"When there is only one set of tracks connecting from station to station, the railway line is called a 'single track'."

【ポーレット】
"For single tracks, going to and from the station uses the same track. So naturally, trains going in opposite directions would collide with one another. If there is an express train trying to overpass a regular train, one will rear end the other. In order to prevent that, one of the trains must evacuate to the side to let the other pass."

【ハチロク】
"The short amount of tracks to evacuate from the main tracks is called the sidetrack."
