Crosstie
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Crossties are the longitudinal wooden blocks that serve as a shock absorber for the tracks. They are placed on top of the [:バラスト]ballast[:] and then spikes are hammered into them to affix the rails to them."

【ポーレット】
"Crossties and [:バラスト]ballast[:] reduce vibrations felt by the [:列車]train[:]. Actually, without crossties and [:バラスト]ballast[:], the rails would most likely continue to sink into the ground from the weight of the [:列車]train[:]."
