Conductor
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"Like the [:機関士]engineer[:] and driver, the conductor is responsible for the safety of the [:列車]train[:]. At the former [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:], they were called Rechi, among other names."

【ポーレット】
"The job of the conductor is mostly dealing with passengers and freight. They do safety checks around the door and also guide passengers, ticketing on the railcar, and also dealing with the [:緩急車]caboose[:]. Also, they take the place of stationmasters in unmanned stations."

【ハチロク】
"In short, they confirm departure signals and call out for it. A conductor's job has many facets to it, so during long range trips, having a good conductor provides peace of mind for both the [:機関士]engineer[:] and [:レイルロオド]Raillord[:]."
