Train
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"There are two main definitions for the word 'train'. One is a railcar formation with more than two cars. Another is a railcar that runs on the tracks according to the diagram."

【ポーレット】
"For example, if [:キハ07]Kiha 07[:] is not connected to any other railcar in a single car [:編成]formation[:], it is only called a train if it runs on the tracks following the diagram."

【ハチロク】
"For more details, see the entry on [:編成]formation[:]."
