Ballast
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The ballast is the crushed rock that is laid below the [:枕木]crossties[:] of the tracks in order to reduce the shock on the tracks themselves."

【双鉄】
"On the other hand, it also reduces the vibrations and noise from the running [:列車]train[:]. The ballast is small, but it serves an important function that you do not see."
