First- and Second-class Passenger Car
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"As the name implies, there is first-class and second-class seating on the same passenger car. Although it is more proper to call it a first-class/second-class composite car."

【ポーレット】
"Ohitoyo Railway doesn't have the Green Car system, so first-class will be reserved seating while second-class will be free seating. For railway companies with Green Cars, first-class is Green, second-class is reserved, and regular is free seating."
