Steam Drainage
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The steam used to move the [:蒸気機関車]steam engine[:] will condense back into water when cooled. [:蒸気機関車]Steam engines[:] with a device called a steam condenser can circulate that water, but on [:8620]8620[:], the water will be discarded as drainage."

【双鉄】
"The cooled water is exhausted out as steam drainage. Quite literal if you ask me."
