Train Photo Enthusiast
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"This kind of railway fan takes pictures of trains and railway industry related things as a hobby. They are called the train photo enthusiast."

【ハチロク】
"During the [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:] era, you can see them everywhere from the [:運転台]driver stand[:]. Recently, I've begun to see a few from time to time in Ohitoyo."
