Driving Plan
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"[:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] suggest a driving plan based on the number of passengers at each station, and consider the towing capacity and other factors."

【ポーレット】
"However, for a railway company, this only applies when there are passengers. The train schedule set up is made to be most convenient for the passengers. The most efficient plan isn't always the plan used."

【ハチロク】
"That is why the driving plan thought of by [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] are always corrected by people who use the train in reality. And the [:レイルロオド]Raillord[:] will correct any mistakes by those people, allowing the driving plan to be constantly improved upon."
