Maitetsu
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"The kind of railway fans that personally own railcars are called maitetsu. Ever since the Track Closure Era, railway companies have cooperated with maitetsu to stay, though just barely, in operation."

【ハチロク】
"The tracks and stations would be maintained by the railway company while the railcars and [:レイルロオド]Raillords[:] would be maintained by the maitetsu. It was a bold attempt, but it was actually quite effective."

【ポーレット】
"The one who thought up the system is actually Aki-sama of Mouri, the Train Princess. Considering that, had it not been for her, the railways would have declined even more past the Track Closure Era."
