Hearth
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The hearth is the floor of [:火室]firebox[:]. It's the section where coal is directly scattered in. It's also called the [:火格子]grate[:]."

【双鉄】
"By scattering the coal evenly in the hearth, Increasing the combustion efficiency is crucial. A gust blows through the door, so when shoveling, you layer the coal thick at the front and lower at the deep end, or the coal won't burn evenly."

【ハチロク】
"That is why the hearth's state is dependent on the skill of the [:機関助士]engineer assistant[:] and the effects are clear."
