Eater Enthusiast
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ポーレット】
"This type of railway fan mostly travels by railway and eats the specialties and station lunch boxes of the destinations as their hobby."

【双鉄】
"Hm? How is that different from the station lunch box enthusiast?"

【ポーレット】
"The station lunch box enthusiast is only interested in the station lunch box and doesn't use the railways to travel. For example, they're okay to go to the station lunch box festivals to just go and eat. It's a different kind of enthusiast."
