Kiha 07
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【れいな】
"Kiha 07 is the former [:帝鉄]Imperial Railway[:] Model Kiha 07 [:気動車]railcar[:]. It's originally a gasoline [:気動車]railcar[:] with another name, but with the modification into a [:ディーゼル気動車]diesel railcar[:], it was renamed to Kiha 07."

【ポーレット】
"It's distinctive round body and head along with the round eyes give it a cuteness combination. We have two round eyes, but type with a headlight on the forehead is also very cute."

【れいな】
"It's not just with the lights. There are many types of Kiha 07 with many types of modifications. There's also a natural gas [:気動車]railcar[:] and even one that's an electric [:気動車]railcar[:]. It's able to run to all sorts of places that way."
