Smoke Collection Device
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【ハチロク】
"The smoke of a [:蒸気機関車]steam locomotive[:] is extremely dangerous when inside a tunnel. Smoke will get into the [:運転台]driver stand[:] and linger to suffocate the [:機関士]engineer[:] and [:機関助士]engineer assistant[:], impairing operation."

【双鉄】
"Even outside the tunnel, the soot has fire sparks in it that can cause fires."

【ハチロク】
"Correct. That is why smoke must be gathered and its flow must be controlled. And this device does that when it is attached to the chimney with a lid to open on will and to deflect smoke only to the back. This is that smoke collection device."
