Tipple
*解説
;--------------------------------------------------------
【れいな】
"The tipple is the place where coal is sorted. But it's not screened on quality, but more along the lines of separating coal from coal chips, gravel, and pieces of copper wire."

【双鉄】
"Copper wire? Why would that be in it?"

【れいな】
"When dynamite is used excavate, copper wire is used to explode it. That's why there are edges of the copper wire attached to the unexploded dynamite at times in the tipple."
